railbirds.com 2016-10-28

# Railbirds™ - Poker Community

**WHO ARE WE?**  
The Railbirds website is run by Soluan Investments Limited and its group companies (referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we", "us" and "our") to provide our members and others (referred to as "you" and "your") with access to a range of internet-based services. The website lets you communicate across the internet in various ways. This includes forums, blogs, mail, diaries etc. 

We take privacy and confidentiality seriously and recognise that, when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible way. To help you understand what we will do with your information we have developed this Privacy Policy. It will enable us to protect your personal information and will help you to feel comfortable about registering as a member and using our website. By using and visiting our website and using our services you agree to this Privacy Policy.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**  
As a member you will be able to maintain two different profiles on Railbirds. One is your public profile, which contains the information that can be viewed by anyone. The other is your private profile, which contains information which only you and we can see. You use these profiles to access the website and post information on the site, these postings may also contain personal information about you. 

Any information you provide us is given voluntarily by you, and it is up to you to decide what information you post on the site. You should think carefully about what information you give us and what information you make available for other members to see. In particular, think carefully before providing particularly private information such as information about your health, and before providing any details that would allow other members to contact you other than through the website - such as your home telephone number.   

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW DO WE USE IT?**

To register as a member of the website, you will have to provide us with your: 

  * age
  * gender (male or female)
  * location (city and country)
  * e-mail address

We need this to register you and to provide you with access to our services.

You can then voluntarily provide us with more information if you wish to amend your member profile, for example you may give us your postal address and mobile number. You may also wish to place messages or pictures onto the website. What you post on the website is also covered by our Terms of Service and you should make sure you agree to these and understand them before you register. 

**General use of your information**

We will use the personal details you give us, and information we obtain from other sources, to provide you with the services you have signed up for, to run the website and our services and to provide customer services support for you. We will also use information for marketing, to monitor your use of the services and the website and to make sure that the content, services and advertising that we offer are tailored to your needs and interests. 

We may keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes. We may need to share your information with our service providers and agents for these purposes. We may disclose personal data to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation. 

**Improving the website and tracking use of our website**

We intend to continue improving the content and function of the website and we like to be able to make sure that advertising on the website is suitable for our members. For this reason, we look at member traffic patterns and use of the website to help us improve the design and layout of our site and provide content of interest to you. We may disclose statistical information to our advertisers to be able to show them, for example, how many people use the website, how old they are and where they are from, but this will not have any names or other identifying details about you.   
**  
How long do we keep your information for?**

Information you give us will be kept for varying time periods depending on its nature. Some examples are:

Guest book entries will be removed after a certain level is reached or after a certain time period has expired;  
Other information will remain as long as your user account remains active;  
After 3 months of inactivity on your account, basic data (such as age, gender and nickname) will be archived but will never be deleted. Similarly, information about the user account will never be deleted.

**USE OF COOKIES**  
We may use information obtained about you using cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you open an email from us or visit our site in future. We do this to remember your preferences, identify you and personalise the site for you where possible. Cookies store small pieces of information about visitors such as email addresses and names. We can therefore identify you when you return to the site and welcome you back. 

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. If you want to stop cookies being stored on your computer in the future, please refer to your browser manufacturer's instructions by clicking "Help" in your browser menu. 

Further information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site. 

When you visit our site, we may also log your IP address, which is a way of identifying your unique computer or other access device.

**YOUR CONSENT**  
By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our processing your personal data for the purposes mentioned above (including any sensitive personal data that you provide us with).

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**  
We offer the use of a secure server when you use our website or access your account information. We always take appropriate measures to ensure that the information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used (as set out above).

**OTHER INFORMATION**  
If you would like to see a copy of the information we hold about you, you may ask us for it. We may charge a small fee for this. You are also entitled to correct any inaccuracies in the information we hold about you. You can change your information in the Private Settings section of the website. 

Please note that any communications you have with us may be recorded for training or quality control purposes.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**  
Your privacy and your opinions are very important to us.

If you have any comments or opinions; or  
If you have any questions about the way we hold and use your information  
Please contact us by sending an email to privacy@railbirds.com.

**NOTE:**  
This privacy policy may change from time to time. You should check it regularly to make sure you have seen the most recent version. We will notify you of any changes where we are required to do so, and unless you cancel your membership your continued use of the site will be considered acceptance of the latest version of this Privacy Policy.
